(guitar strumming)
♪ Johnny's in the basement,
mixin' up the medicine ♪
♪ I'm on the pavement,
thinkin' about the government ♪
♪ The man in a trench
coat, badge out, laid off ♪
♪ Says he's got a bad cough,
wants to get it paid off ♪
♪ Look out, kid, it's somethin' you did ♪
♪ God knows when, but
you're doin' it again ♪
♪ You better duck down the alleyway ♪
♪ Looking for a new friend ♪
♪ The man in the coon-skin
cap in a pig pen ♪
♪ Wants 11 dollar bills, you only got 10 ♪
♪ Maggie comes fleet foot,
face full of black soot ♪
♪ Talkin' that the heat put
plants in the bed, but ♪
♪ Phone's tapped anyway ♪
♪ Maggie says the many say ♪
♪ They must bust in early May ♪
♪ Orders from the D.A. ♪
♪ Look out, kid, don't
matter what you did ♪
♪ Walk on your tip toes,
don't tie no bows ♪
♪ Better stay away from those
that carry around a fire hose ♪
♪ Keep a clean nose,
watch the plainclothes ♪
♪ You don't need a weather man ♪
♪ To know which way the wind blows ♪
♪ Oh, get sick, get well,
hang around a ink well ♪
♪ Hang bail, hard to tell
if anything is gonna sell ♪
♪ Try hard, get barred,
get back, ride rail ♪
♪ Get jailed, jump bail,
join the Army if you fail ♪
♪ Look out, kid, you're gonna get hit ♪
♪ By losers, cheaters, six-time users ♪
♪ Hanging round the theaters ♪
♪ Girl by the whirlpool's
looking for a new fool ♪
♪ Don't follow leaders,
watch the parking meters ♪
♪ Oh, get born, keep warm ♪
♪ Short pants, romance ♪
♪ Learn to dance, get dressed ♪
♪ Get blessed, try to be a success ♪
♪ Please her, please him, buy gifts ♪
♪ Don't steal, don't lift ♪
♪ 20 years of schoolin' and
they put you on the day shift ♪
♪ Look out, kid, they keep it all hid ♪
♪ Better jump down a manhole,
light yourself a candle ♪
♪ Don't wear sandals, try
to avoid the scandals ♪
♪ Don't want to be a bum,
you better chew gum ♪
♪ The pump don't work 'cause
the vandals took the handles ♪